joomlabear.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy-Joomla Bear

##  Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for http://joomlabear.com 

The privacy of our visitors is **extremely important to us**. 

At http://joomlabear.com we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit http://joomlabear.com and how we safeguard your information. 

**We never sell your personal information to third parties**. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Cookies and Web Beacons We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on http://joomlabear.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

This information is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

We hope that you enjoy your visit and find some useful Joomla Templates! 

Please contact us if you have any questions. 

Kind regards, 

Big Bear 

Free porn Movies, HD porn tube [gratis porno](http://www.wichstube.com/ "gratis porno") And German porn movies HD videos. Best Videos and High Quailty Porn All Locations Supported. And German sex videos [porn](http://www.pornep.com/ "pornep") Fuck movies [german porno](http://www.freigermanpornos.com/ "german porno"), You porn videos [porn videos](http://www.redhotsexy.com/ "porn videos"), Sex Videos [free porn videos](http://www.pornwet.com/ "free porn videos"), i like porn videos [porn](http://www.pornzr.com/ "porn") Und Beste porno filme , germany videos [porno](http://www.pornodeu.com/ "porno") , neu german porns [neu pornos](http://www.neuporno.com/ "neu pornos")

### Who's Online

We have 189 guests and 7 bears online 

### Joomla Template Blog

  * ### [Shareasale Review – 3 Good Reasons Why This Affiliate Network Shines](http://blog.joomlabear.com/shareasale-why-i-love-working-with-them-to-monetize-my-websites/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=shareasale-why-i-love-working-with-them-to-monetize-my-websites)

12 Nov 2011 | 10:04 pm

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/shareasale-why-i-love-working-with-them-to-monetize-my-websites/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=shareasale-why-i-love-working-with-them-to-monetize-my-websites) Disclosure: The links to Shareasale in this article are affiliate links. If you choose to sign up with Shareasale, as either a merchant or affiliate, Joomlabear may receive some compensation[…] 

  * ### [Motion Theme – A New Template Compatible with Joomla 1.7](http://blog.joomlabear.com/motion-theme-a-new-template-compatible-with-joomla-1-7/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=motion-theme-a-new-template-compatible-with-joomla-1-7)

27 Jul 2011 | 8:18 pm

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/motion-theme-a-new-template-compatible-with-joomla-1-7/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=motion-theme-a-new-template-compatible-with-joomla-1-7) Update: Motion Theme for Joomla 1.7 Released – Click here to read details and download. Last year I blogged about converting the amazing Motion WordPress theme to Joomla. We’re now[…] 

  * ### [Updates to TransparentBliss 3 Released](http://blog.joomlabear.com/updates-to-transparentbliss-3-released/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=updates-to-transparentbliss-3-released)

29 Jun 2011 | 10:54 am

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/updates-to-transparentbliss-3-released/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=updates-to-transparentbliss-3-released) Updated TransparentBliss 3 The template is currently available to premium members, and can be downloaded here. ————————————— Layout Selection -Layout Selection in the Template Options (Less-Transparent, More-Transparent, Square-Corners) Layout Problem[…] 

  * ### [Bears and Motorcycles are a Bad Mix](http://blog.joomlabear.com/bears-and-motorcycles-are-a-bad-mix/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=bears-and-motorcycles-are-a-bad-mix)

27 Jun 2011 | 8:23 pm

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/bears-and-motorcycles-are-a-bad-mix/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=bears-and-motorcycles-are-a-bad-mix) For those of you who don’t me, I’m Lachlan MacKinven, also known as Big Bear here at Joomlabear. I founded Joomlabear with my brother, Alexis, in 2007. This post is[…] 

  * ### [How To Edit Images On Joomla](http://blog.joomlabear.com/how-to-edit-images-on-joomla/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=how-to-edit-images-on-joomla)

12 Jul 2010 | 3:46 am

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/how-to-edit-images-on-joomla/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=how-to-edit-images-on-joomla) I just wanted to make some notes about editing images for the web. A few users have had trouble with it. And I often take what I know for granted,[…] 

  * ### [Easter News – April Joomlabear Newsletter – Web Edition](http://blog.joomlabear.com/easter-news-april-joomlabear-newsletter-web-edition/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=easter-news-april-joomlabear-newsletter-web-edition)

1 Apr 2010 | 8:03 pm

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/easter-news-april-joomlabear-newsletter-web-edition/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=easter-news-april-joomlabear-newsletter-web-edition) Happy Easter everyone, from all the team at JoomlaBear. We have a few Easter eggs for you, and plenty of stuff to talk about, Joomulus, Joomla template updates, new team[…] 

  * ### [Joomulus Updated](http://blog.joomlabear.com/joomulus-updated/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=joomulus-updated)

1 Apr 2010 | 3:06 pm

[ ](http://blog.joomlabear.com/joomulus-updated/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=joomulus-updated) Joomulus has been updated and fixes a possible XSS attack vulnerability. Please download the update now, and please ensure that all Tag URL’s you enter into the module parameters include[…]
